GEORGE KOURTIS

WEB DEVELOPER

< >

Currently learning: React.js



fir

in /george-kourtis

About Me:

Creative web developer dedicated to developing and optimizing interactive, user-friendly and feature-rich websites. Leverage analytical skills and strong attention to detail in order to deliver original and efficient web solutions, provide technical knowledge and expertise. Willing to contribute to the goals of the business.

Education:

• IEK AKMI | SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Software Technician: Application development and analysis, database design and management. 2016 - 2019 | Thessaloniki

Northwind Data Recovery:

Hard Disk Data Recovery (RAID, HD, SSD) Ransomware Virus Analysis

2016 | Thessaloniki

Digital Marketing ADMINE S.A:
 Functional analysis of search adds (google ads),
 SEO Tools, Social Media Marketing.

 2017 | Thessaloniki

Work Experience:

• City Hall - Katerini:

Information and Communication Technologies: -- Maintenance of applications and databases.

2018 - 2019

• NetFace - Digital Marketing:

Website Design & Promotion Company: -- Frontend Developement UI / UX Design

2020 - 2022

• Webbrain - Web Agency (Remote)

Website Design & Promotion Company: -- Frontend Development UI / UX Design

June 2021 - Oktober 2021 | Naxos Island, Greece

Contact Infomation:

gkourtis55@gmail.com

🏚 💮 Ploutarxou 10 | Katerini GR

+30 6986764436

2-11-1997

Programming Skills & Frameworks:













CMS - Contect Management Systems:







Work Environments:

Visual Studio Code / Figma UI / UX / Microsoft Office / Plesk / Photoshop / Illustrator / After Effects / Github CLI / Node (npm)

Languages:

Greek (Native Language)
English (Advanced TOEIC B2 | State Degree B2)

Military Services:

Fullfilled: 17/08/2019 | 17/06/2020 Special Forces at BMK - Naousa Imathia